[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the longest running primetime television show in the period 1950-2009?", "correct_answer": "Hallmark Hall of Fame", "incorrect_answers": ["Monday Night Football", "The Simpsons", "60 Minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the capital city of the U.S. state of Wyoming.", "correct_answer": "Cheyenne", "incorrect_answers": ["Boise", "Des Moines", "Salt Lake City"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of the famous husband and wife detective team from the series of Thin Man movies?", "correct_answer": "Charles", "incorrect_answers": ["Marple", "Powell", "Queen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award did the 1989 drama movie My Left Foot receive?", "correct_answer": "Award for Best Actor", "incorrect_answers": ["Award for Best Director", "Award for Best Picture", "Award for Best Supporting Actor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Coach Herb Brooks tragically lost his life after the filming of the movie Miracle, in which he was a consultant.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie, featuring Viggo Mortenson, does Ed Harris co-star as the ruthless one-eyed Carl Fogarty?", "correct_answer": "A History of Violence", "incorrect_answers": ["Eastern Promises", "Carlitos Way", "China Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The consumption of which of these mammals is forbidden by Jewish laws?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Hare", "Camel", "Pig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "NASAs Chandra space observatory launched on July 23, 1999 uses what type of telescopes?", "correct_answer": "X-ray telescopes", "incorrect_answers": ["Optical telescopes", "Infrared telescopes", "Radio telescopes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1897, American scientist John Jacob Abel was able to isolate which of the following?", "correct_answer": "adrenaline", "incorrect_answers": ["cocaine", "ACTH", "human growth hormone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of conic section would this equation yield: (x^2)/9-(y^2)/4=81?", "correct_answer": "Hyperbola", "incorrect_answers": ["Ray", "Line", "Parabola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did the American Airlines Flight 965 crash into on December 20, 1995 in Colombia?", "correct_answer": "Mountain", "incorrect_answers": ["Another plane", "Village", "Skyscraper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the second most important vegetable fibre after cotton that is woven to make coarse cloth and sacks?", "correct_answer": "Jute", "incorrect_answers": ["Juniper", "Jade", "Jet"]}]